cuttingedgeoffers.com 2002-12-04

# Cutting Edge Offers

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY:**

Because Cutting Edge Offers, and all of it's subsidiary domains, want to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and notify you of: 

  1. The organization collecting the information.
  2. How the information is used.
  3. With whom the information may be shared.
  4. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  5. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Cutting Edge Offers's control.
  6. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact [postmaster@Cutting Edge Offers](mailto:postmaster@cuttingedgeoffers.com) by email.

Cutting Edge Offers has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

Cutting Edge Offers takes the issue of online privacy very seriously. Please study the information below carefully. It details our policies with regard to privacy and informs you of your rights.

How is my member information used?  
Is my personal information shared with outside persons or companies?  
How secure is your site?  
How secure are the links available on your site?  
What if I choose to opt out of receiving advertisements?  
Do you use cookies?  
What about cookies from your advertisers?  

You will receive emails regarding offers from trusted partners. You can elect to opt out simply by clicking on the unsubscribe link that appears at the bottom of the email you will receive. The email you receive may include offers, promotions and materials from many sources and sponsors, for which management of this website accepts no responsibility. 

_back to top_

The personal information submitted by you remains your property. When you voluntarily submit personally identifiable information, you grant us the right to make use of that information for marketing purposes. You also consent to receive email from us regarding various events or promotions. You also grant us the right to share our email list with other businesses in order to bring selected retail opportunities to you.

You agree that we may share your personal information with our partners, sponsors, advertisers, service providers and marketers for marketing promotions, lookup and reference services applications, and other entities that we believe can provide you with special offers and opportunities. 

We reserve the right to release user information internally within Cutting Edge Offers. We also reserve the right to release current or past member information to third parties for limited purposes in the following instances (i) when required by law; (ii) to protect Cutting Edge Offers's rights or property; (iii) in the event that the stock or assets of Cutting Edge Offers is sold or acquired; (iv) to protect the personal safety of our users or the public; and (iv) pursuant to a court or administrative order. We may also use such information to fulfill prizes, track compliance with our Rules, or for content improvement and feedback purposes. We are free to disclose aggregate user information to third parties.

_back to top_

To safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, Cutting Edge Offers uses industry-standard efforts such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers where appropriate. We also employ strict security procedures that protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. Access to data is limited and strictly enforced. Additionally, we continually review our security measures to ensure your identity is adequately protected. 

_back to top_

While we make every effort to ensure that we deal only with ethical companies, please be aware that our privacy policy does not extend to sites linked from Cutting Edge Offers. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any Web site. 

_back to top_

If at any time you change your mind about receiving advertising and email updates from Cutting Edge Offers, then click here to unsubscribe.

_back to top_

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. We use cookies for various purposes so that we can present you with customized content and ads that will likely be of more interest to you. 

_back to top_

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on written by your browser. We do not control, nor do we have access to any of the information they may collect. Cutting Edge Offers serves ads from third parties on our site. These ads may contain cookies. This policy only covers the use of cookies by Cutting Edge Offers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Cutting Edge Offers does not have control, nor access to the information contained in its advertisers cookies. 

_back to top_
